Guide to the Archives Information File, Section 5: Boxes 89-101
Archives Information File, Section 5: Boxes 89-101
- Box: 91, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 91, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Public Law 89-136, 1965; Publication (Box 91, Folder 11)
    Notes: August 26, 1965
- Box: 91, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 91, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Amendments to the Railroad Retirement Act, 1963; Publication (Box 91, Folder 12)
    Notes: September 12, 1963
  - Item 2: Amending the Railroad Retirement Act, 1966; Publication (Box 91, Folder 12)
    Notes: October 1, 1966
  - Item 3: Amendments to the Railroad Retirement Act, 1959; Publication (Box 91, Folder 12)
    Notes: March 23, 1959
  - Item 4: Amending the Railroad Retirement Act, 1966; Publication (Box 91, Folder 12)
  - Item 5: Amend Railway Retirement Legislation, 1966; Publication (Box 91, Folder 12)
    Notes: May 18, 1966
- Box: 91, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 91, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Public Law 89-456, 1966; Publication (Box 91, Folder 13)
    Notes: June 20, 1966
  - Item 2: Railway Labor Act, Publication (Box 91, Folder 13)
  - Item 3: Railway Labor Act, Publication (Box 91, Folder 13)
- Box: 91, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 91, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Social Security Amendments, Publication (Box 91, Folder 14)
    Author: U.S. Department of Agriculture
  - Item 2: Health Insurance, 1965; Publication (Box 91, Folder 14)
    Notes: July 30, 1965
  - Item 3: The Benefits of Social Security, Publication (Box 91, Folder 14)
    Author: Council of Profit Sharing Industries
  - Item 4: Social Security Amendments, Publication (Box 91, Folder 14)
  - Item 5: Public Law 90-248, 1968; Publication (Box 91, Folder 14)
    Notes: January 2, 1968
  - Item 6: Major Provisions, 1965; Publication (Box 91, Folder 14)
    Author: U.S. Committee on Finance
- Box: 91, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 91, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: The Trade Expansion Act, Publication (Box 91, Folder 15)
  - Item 2: Assistance for Workers, Publication (Box 91, Folder 15)
- Box: 91, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 91, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: The Vocational Education Act, Publication (Box 91, Folder 16)
- Box: 91, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 91, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Amending the Vocational Rehabilitation Act, 1966; Publication (Box 91, Folder 17)
    Notes: October 7, 1966
  - Item 2: The Vocational Rehabilitation Act, Publication (Box 91, Folder 17)
  - Item 3: Vocational Rehabilitation Act, 1966; Publication (Box 91, Folder 17)
    Notes: December 1966
- Box: 91, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 91, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Rights of Pension Plan Participants, Publication (Box 91, Folder 18)
  - Item 2: Amending Certain Provisions of the Welfare and Pension Plans Disclosure Act, 1966; Publication (Box 91, Folder 18)
    Notes: September 1, 1966
- Box: 91, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 91, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Rules and Regulations, 1947; Publication (Box 91, Folder 19)
    Notes: August 22, 1947
  - Item 2: Problems of the National Labor Relations Board, Publication (Box 91, Folder 19)
    Author: International Juridical Association
  - Item 3: Jurisdiction and Enforcement Authority of the National War Labor Board, Publication (Box 91, Folder 19)
    Author: U.S. National War Labor Board
- Box: 91, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 91, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Congressional Oversight of Administrative Agencies, 1970; Publication (Box 91, Folder 20)
- Box: 91, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 91, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: The National Labor Relations Board, 1970; Publication (Box 91, Folder 21)
    Author: Joseph F. Fulton
    Notes: November 13, 1970
- Box: 91, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 91, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: William Randolph Hearst's Views on NRA, Publication (Box 91, Folder 23)
    Author: William Randolph Hearst
- Box: 91, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 91, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Contract Award Procedures and Practices of the Office of Economic Opportunity Need Improving, 1971; Publication (Box 91, Folder 24)
    Notes: December 15, 1971
- Box: 91, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 91, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Improvements Needed in Training and Technical Assistance Services Provided to Antipoverty Agencies, 1972; Publication (Box 91, Folder 25)
    Notes: April 26, 1972
- Box: 91, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 91, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Graphic Presentation of Federal Employment, 1959; Publication (Box 91, Folder 26)
    Notes: December 1959
  - Item 2: Current Manpower Issues in the Federal Government, 1965; Publication (Box 91, Folder 26)
    Notes: August 1965
  - Item 3: Federal Political Executives, Publication (Box 91, Folder 26)
    Author: Brookings Institution
  - Item 4: Graphic Presentation of Federal Employment, 1961; Publication (Box 91, Folder 26)
    Notes: March 1961
  - Item 5: Rights and Responsibilities, 1967; Publication (Box 91, Folder 26)
    Notes: January 22, 1967
  - Item 6: Occupations of Federal Blue-Collar Workers, 1966; Publication (Box 91, Folder 26)
    Notes: October 31, 1966
  - Item 7: Improving Executive Management in the Federal Government, Publication (Box 91, Folder 26)
  - Item 8: Salary and Retirement Annuity Increases, 1971; Publication (Box 91, Folder 26)
    Notes: January 1971
  - Item 9: Federal Civilian Employment by Country, 1960; Publication (Box 91, Folder 26)
    Author: U.S. Joint Committee on Reduction of Nonessential Federal Expenditures
    Notes: December 31, 1960
  - Item 10: Occupations of Federal Blue-Collar Workers, 1960; Publication (Box 91, Folder 26)
    Notes: October 31, 1960
  - Item 11: Californians in Federal Government Employment, 1966; Publication (Box 91, Folder 26)
    Author: California Department of Industrial Relations
    Notes: August 1966
  - Item 12: Detail of Employees From Field Service to Departmental Service, 1966; Publication (Box 91, Folder 26)
    Notes: October 6, 1966
  - Item 13: Mobilizing to Meet Municipal Manpower Challenges, Publication (Box 91, Folder 26)
    Author: Public Personnel Association
  - Item 14: Protecting Privacy and the Rights of Federal Employees, 1967; Publication (Box 91, Folder 26)
    Notes: August 21, 1967
  - Item 15: Problems of Federal Retirees, 1971; Publication (Box 91, Folder 26)
    Notes: June 23, 1971
  - Item 16: Federal Employee Legislation, 1971; Publication (Box 91, Folder 26)
  - Item 17: Federal Employee Bonding Requirements, 1971; Publication (Box 91, Folder 26)
    Notes: April 7, 1971
  - Item 18: Grade Trand of Federal Civilian Employment, 1969; Publication (Box 91, Folder 26)
    Notes: June 1969
  - Item 19: Federal Civilian Employment, Pay, and Benefits, Publication (Box 91, Folder 26)
    Author: Tax Foundation
- Box: 91, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 91, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Federal Government Employment Principles, Publication (Box 91, Folder 27)
    Author: U.S. Retraining and Reemployment Administration
- Box: 91, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 91, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Management and the Marginal Employee, 1966; Publication (Box 91, Folder 28)
    Author: Federal Council for Science and Technology
    Notes: March 1966
  - Item 2: Supergrade Requirements, 1967; Publication (Box 91, Folder 28)
    Notes: June 13, 20, July 13, 27, 1967
  - Item 3: Supergrade Requirements, 1966; Publication (Box 91, Folder 28)
    Notes: February 9, 1966
  - Item 4: Salary Systems of the Federal Service, 1968; Publication (Box 91, Folder 28)
    Notes: September 16-20, 1968
  - Item 5: Extension of Civil service Apportionment Requirement to Temporary Summer Employment, 1965; Publication (Box 91, Folder 28)
    Notes: June 15, 1965
  - Item 6: Coordinated Federal Wage System, 1968; Publication (Box 91, Folder 28)
  - Item 7: Supergrade Positions, 1965; Publication (Box 91, Folder 28)
    Notes: August 25, 1965
  - Item 8: Career Status for Certain Temporary Employees, 1967; Publication (Box 91, Folder 28)
    Notes: May 2-3, 1967
  - Item 9: Downgrading Actions in the Federal Government, 1967; Publication (Box 91, Folder 28)
    Notes: May 3, 1967
  - Item 10: Supergrades, 1968; Publication (Box 91, Folder 28)
  - Item 11: Wage Board Employees, 1967; Publication (Box 91, Folder 28)
    Notes: October 10, 1967
  - Item 12: Employment Rights and Responsibilities of Noncareer Executive Appointees, Publication (Box 91, Folder 28)
  - Item 13: Survey of Probationary Period Practices, Publication (Box 91, Folder 28)
  - Item 14: Your Executive Team, Publication (Box 91, Folder 28)
  - Item 15: Basic Acts, Rules, and Regulations, 1951; Publication (Box 91, Folder 28)
    Notes: January 1951
- Box: 91, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 91, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Directory of Agency Officials, 1967; Publication (Box 91, Folder 29)
    Notes: October 1967
- Box: 91, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 91, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Political Activity, 1961; Publication (Box 91, Folder 30)
    Notes: November 1961
  - Item 2: Federal Pay Legislation, 1970; Publication (Box 91, Folder 30)
    Notes: April 6, 1970
  - Item 3: Federal Salary Comparability Act, 1969; Publication (Box 91, Folder 30)
    Notes: September 9, 1969
  - Item 4: Report of the Advisory Panel on Federal Salary Systems, 1963; Publication (Box 91, Folder 30)
    Notes: August 16, 1963
- Box: 91, Folder: 31, Publication (Box 91, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Salary Table No.46, 1966; Publication (Box 91, Folder 31)
    Notes: July 1966
  - Item 2: The Federal Top Salary Network, 1962; Publication (Box 91, Folder 31)
  - Item 3: Acceptable Level of Competence and Quality Increase Features, 1963; Publication (Box 91, Folder 31)
    Notes: October 1963
  - Item 4: Salary and Retirement Annuity Increases, 1971; Publication (Box 91, Folder 31)
    Notes: May 1971
  - Item 5: Salary Systems of the Federal Service, 1968; Publication (Box 91, Folder 31)
  - Item 6: PHS Commissioned Officers Retirement Equalization, 1970; Publication (Box 91, Folder 31)
    Author: U.S. Committee on Interstate and Foreign Commerce
    Notes: January 28, 1970
  - Item 7: Payment of an Allowance to Federal Employees to Nevada Test Site, 1965; Publication (Box 91, Folder 31)
    Author: U.S. Committee on Government Operations
  - Item 8: Proposed Additional Positions in Supergrade Levels, 1969; Publication (Box 91, Folder 31)
  - Item 9: Increasing Group Life Insurance Coverage for Federal Employees, 1965; Publication (Box 91, Folder 31)
    Notes: June 16, 1965
  - Item 10: Coordinated Federal Wage System, 1968; Publication (Box 91, Folder 31)
  - Item 11: Social Security and Federal Employment, 1965; Publication (Box 91, Folder 31)
    Author: U.S. Committee on Ways and Means
    Notes: March 13, 1965
  - Item 12: The Wage Board System, 1966; Publication (Box 91, Folder 31)
    Author: U.S. Subcommittee on Manpower
  - Item 13: Nomination, 1969; Publication (Box 91, Folder 31)
    Notes: January 16, 1969
  - Item 14: Supergrades, 1969; Publication (Box 91, Folder 31)
    Notes: July 8-9, 1969
  - Item 15: Federal Employees' Compassionate Leave, 1968; Publication (Box 91, Folder 31)
    Notes: May 14, 1968
  - Item 16: Report of the Advisory Panel on Federal Salary Systems, 1963; Publication (Box 91, Folder 31)
  - Item 17: Health Benefits Program, 1968; Publication (Box 91, Folder 31)
    Notes: July 9-10, 1968
  - Item 18: Federal Employee Fringe Benefits, 1968; Publication (Box 91, Folder 31)
  - Item 19: Work Injury Benefits for Federal Employees, 1967; Publication (Box 91, Folder 31)
  - Item 20: Increasing Group Life Insurance Coverage for Federal Employees, 1967; Publication (Box 91, Folder 31)
    Notes: February 7-8, 1967
  - Item 21: Veto of H.R. 17809, 1971; Publication (Box 91, Folder 31)
    Notes: January 2, 1971
  - Item 22: Government Employees' Incentive Awards Act, 1967; Publication (Box 91, Folder 31)
    Notes: November 2, 1967
  - Item 23: Public Law 89-504, 1966; Publication (Box 91, Folder 31)
  - Item 24: Compensation for Selective Service System Employees, 1966; Publication (Box 91, Folder 31)
    Notes: April 18, 1966
  - Item 25: Supergrade Positions, 1969; Publication (Box 91, Folder 31)
    Notes: November 5, 1969
  - Item 26: Pay Comparability System Act, 1969; Publication (Box 91, Folder 31)
    Notes: June 18, 1969
- Box: 92, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Increasing Group Life Insurance Coverage for Federal Employees, 1965; Publication (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Employees' Life Insurance Fund, 1966; Publication (Box 92, Folder 1)
    Notes: September 13, 1966
  - Item 3: Improved Life Insurance Benefits, 1967; Publication (Box 92, Folder 1)
    Notes: May 1-2, 1967
  - Item 4: Improved Life Insurance Benefits, 1966; Publication (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Supergrades, 1968; Publication (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Report Covering the Effectivenes of Implementation, 1967; Publication (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Social Security and Federal Employment, 1965; Publication (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: Government Employees Salary Comparability Act, 1965; Publication (Box 92, Folder 1)
    Notes: August 16, 1965
  - Item 9: Federal Employees' Salary Increases, 1966; Publication (Box 92, Folder 1)
    Notes: May 26, 1966
  - Item 10: Service Credit and Fringe Benefits for ASC Employees, 1965; Publication (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - Item 11: Correction of Certain Employment Inequities with Respect to Premium Compensation, 1966; Publication (Box 92, Folder 1)
    Notes: July 14, 1966
  - Item 12: Back Pay Act, 1965; Publication (Box 92, Folder 1)
    Notes: February 9, 1965
  - Item 13: Federal Employees Salary Act, 1970; Publication (Box 92, Folder 1)
    Notes: October 14, 1970
  - Item 14: Seminar on Federal Incentive Awards Operations, 1967; Publication (Box 92, Folder 1)
    Notes: October 25, 1967
  - Item 15: The Federal Top Salary Network, 1963; Publication (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - Item 16: Group Life, Accident, Medical and Hospital Insurance Programs, 1966; Publication (Box 92, Folder 1)
    Author: U.S. Committee on State and Local Government
    Notes: February 11, 1966
- Box: 92, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 92, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Our American Government, 1965; Publication (Box 92, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: National Issues, Publication (Box 92, Folder 2)
- Box: 92, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The New Deal and Business Recovery, Publication (Box 92, Folder 3)
    Author: Holt, Rinehart, & Winston
  - Item 2: Improving Citizenship Education, Publication (Box 92, Folder 3)
    Author: Columbia University
- Box: 92, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Current Political Pressures on Washington and What They Mean for Business Policy, 1957; Publication (Box 92, Folder 4)
    Notes: March 1957
  - Item 2: Political Roundup 1958, Publication (Box 92, Folder 4)
    Notes: October 1958
- Box: 92, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 92, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Restoration of Effective Sovereignty to Solve Social Problems, 1971; Publication (Box 92, Folder 5)
    Notes: December 6, 1971
  - Item 2: The Concept of Public Policy in the 1970's, Publication (Box 92, Folder 5)
    Author: Daniel P. Moynihan
- Box: 92, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 92, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Population Trends, 1964; Publication (Box 92, Folder 6)
    Author: American Telephone and Telegraph Company
  - Item 2: Out Population Explosion, 1962; Publication (Box 92, Folder 6)
    Author: Center for Information on America
  - Item 3: The Need for New Cities, Publication (Box 92, Folder 6)
    Author: Bow Group
- Box: 92, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 92, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: More Effective Use of Manpower and Machines Recommended in Mechanized Post Offices, 1971; Publication (Box 92, Folder 7)
    Notes: May 27, 1971
- Box: 92, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 92, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Comments on the President's 1967 Economic Report, Publication (Box 92, Folder 8)
    Author: The American Bankers Association
- Box: 92, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 92, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: U.S. Community Improvement Appraisal, 1939; Publication (Box 92, Folder 9)
    Author: National Appraisal Committee
    Notes: April 1939
- Box: 92, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 92, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Taxes and the Budget, 1947; Publication (Box 92, Folder 10)
    Author: Communitee for Economic Development
    Notes: November 1947
- Box: 92, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 92, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: We Don't Help Blacks by Hurting Whites, Publication (Box 92, Folder 11)
    Author: League for Industrial Democracy
  - Item 2: Guidelines: A Manual for Bi-Racial Committees, Publication (Box 92, Folder 11)
    Author: Anti-Defamation League of B'Nai B'Rith
- Box: 92, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 92, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Negro-Jewish Relations, Publication (Box 92, Folder 12)
- Box: 92, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 92, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: The Rural Society in Transition, 1966; Publication (Box 92, Folder 13)
    Author: Ernest J. Nesius
    Notes: April 1966
- Box: 92, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 92, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: The Urban Crisis, Publication (Box 92, Folder 14)
    Author: The American Federationist
  - Item 2: The Disjointed Trio, Publication (Box 92, Folder 14)
    Author: California Department of Social Welfare
  - Item 3: For the Right to a Job, Publication (Box 92, Folder 14)
    Author: The Worker
  - Item 4: Converging Social Trends; Emerging Social Problems, Publication (Box 92, Folder 14)
  - Item 5: Social Development, Publication (Box 92, Folder 14)
  - Item 6: One-Third of a Nation, Publication (Box 92, Folder 14)
    Author: The President's Task Force on Manpower Conservation
- Box: 92, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 92, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: First Things First, Publication (Box 92, Folder 15)
    Author: Walter P. Reuther
- Box: 92, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 92, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: The Federal Budget and "The General Welfare", 1959; Publication (Box 92, Folder 16)
  - Item 2: Social Policy for the Nineteen Seventies, Publication (Box 92, Folder 16)
- Box: 92, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 92, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Improved Statistics for Economic Growth, 1966; Publication (Box 92, Folder 17)
- Box: 92, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 92, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Manpower Planning Data, 1972; Publication (Box 92, Folder 18)
    Author: U.S. Veterans Administration
    Notes: March 1972
- Box: 92, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 92, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Chronology of the War Production Board and Predecessor Agencies, Publication (Box 92, Folder 19)
    Author: U.S. Civilian Production Administration
  - Item 2: War Production Drive, Publication (Box 92, Folder 19)
    Author: U.S. War Production Board
  - Item 3: Guide to War Production Drive Representatives on the Formation of Local and Area Councils of Labor, 1944; Publication (Box 92, Folder 19)
    Notes: September 11, 1944
- Box: 92, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 92, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: The WIN II Program, Publication (Box 92, Folder 20)
- Box: 92, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 92, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: The Impact of the Universal Declaration of Human Rights, Publication (Box 92, Folder 21)
    Author: United Nations
- Box: 92, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 92, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: United Nations' Universal Declaration of Human Rights, 1949; Publication (Box 92, Folder 22)
    Notes: July 1949
  - Item 2: Memorandum on the Universal Declaration of Human Rights, Publication (Box 92, Folder 22)
    Author: American Association for the United Nations
  - Item 3: Freedom's Charter, Publication (Box 92, Folder 22)
    Author: Foreign Policy Association
  - Item 4: Human Rights, 1949; Publication (Box 92, Folder 22)
  - Item 5: You Hold the Key to Human Rights, Publication (Box 92, Folder 22)
    Author: The Methodist Church
- Box: 92, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 92, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Campus-Society, Publication (Box 92, Folder 23)
    Author: Lawrence H. Davis
- Box: 92, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 92, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Land-Grant Colleges and Universities, Publication (Box 92, Folder 24)
  - Item 2: The University in America, Publication (Box 92, Folder 24)
  - Item 3: Teaching and Research in the University of Tomorrow, Publication (Box 92, Folder 24)
  - Item 4: How Good Are Our Colleges?, 1938; Publication (Box 92, Folder 24)
    Author: Goodwin Watson
  - Item 5: Institutions of Higher Education, 1972; Publication (Box 92, Folder 24)
    Notes: February 1972
- Box: 92, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 92, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Report by the Governor's Committee on New Jersey Higher Education, Publication (Box 92, Folder 25)
    Author: Governor's Committee on New Jersey Higher Education
- Box: 92, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 92, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: How College Presidents Are Chosen, Publication (Box 92, Folder 26)
    Author: Frederick Bolman
  - Item 2: Cooperative Projects Among Colleges and Universities, Publication (Box 92, Folder 26)
  - Item 3: Internal Structure, Publication (Box 92, Folder 26)
  - Item 4: Roles and Values of Students, 1964; Publication (Box 92, Folder 26)
    Author: International Christian University
    Notes: July 1964
- Box: 92, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 92, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Undergraduate Curriculum Patterns, Publication (Box 92, Folder 27)
  - Item 2: The Neo-Liberal Arts, Publication (Box 92, Folder 27)
    Author: U.S. National Student Association
  - Item 3: Organized Occupational Curriculums, Publication (Box 92, Folder 27)
- Box: 92, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 92, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Summary Report, 1961; Publication (Box 92, Folder 28)
    Notes: December 1961
  - Item 2: University Professors, 1971; Publication (Box 92, Folder 28)
    Author: University of Toronto
  - Item 3: Faculty Work Load, Publication (Box 92, Folder 28)
  - Item 4: Women in College and University Teaching, Publication (Box 92, Folder 28)
    Author: University of Wisconsin
  - Item 5: The Part-Time College Teacher, 1961; Publication (Box 92, Folder 28)
    Author: D.B. Gowin
  - Item 6: Sabbatical Leave in American Higher Education, Publication (Box 92, Folder 28)
  - Item 7: Cooperative-Research, Publication (Box 92, Folder 28)
  - Item 8: How to Measure Faculty Work Load, Publication (Box 92, Folder 28)
    Author: John E. Stecklein
- Box: 92, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 92, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: College and University Endowment Status and Management, Publication (Box 92, Folder 29)
- Box: 92, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 92, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: State Formula for the Support of Public 2-Year Colleges, Publication (Box 92, Folder 30)
  - Item 2: Basic Student Charges, Publication (Box 92, Folder 30)
  - Item 3: Summary Report of Financial Statistics of Institutions of Higher Education, 1962; Publication (Box 92, Folder 30)
- Box: 92, Folder: 31, Publication (Box 92, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Graduate Education, Publication (Box 92, Folder 31)
- Box: 92, Folder: 32, Publication (Box 92, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Higher Education and Economic And Social Development in Latin America, 1962; Publication (Box 92, Folder 32)
    Author: Pan American Union
- Box: 92, Folder: 33, Publication (Box 92, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: Investments in the Future, 1960; Publication (Box 92, Folder 33)
    Author: New York State University
    Notes: December 1960
  - Item 2: New York State and Private Higher Education, 1968; Publication (Box 92, Folder 33)
- Box: 92, Folder: 34, Publication (Box 92, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: Planning for College in New York State, Publication (Box 92, Folder 34)
- Box: 92, Folder: 35, Publication (Box 92, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: College and University Enrollment, 1963; Publication (Box 92, Folder 35)
    Notes: December 1963
- Box: 92, Folder: 36, Publication (Box 92, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: Standards for Professional Staff Preparation and Compensation in College Union Work, 1971; Publication (Box 92, Folder 36)
    Author: Association of College Unions
- Box: 93, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: College Facts Chart, Publication (Box 93, Folder 1)